In the previous lesson,
في الدرس السابق،
you learned some basic principles about representing data graphically.
تعلمت بعض المبادئ الأساسية حول تمثيل البيانات بيانيًا.
Now you're going to learn how to design your visualizations.
وستتعلم الآن كيفية تصميم المرئيات الخاصة بك.
Proper design is essential to convey your story to others.
كما أن التصميم السليم ضروري لنقل قصتك إلى الآخرين.
Check out this thing, it's saying something.
تحقق من هذا الشيء، إنه يشير إلى شيء ما.
What are these wedges indicating, I don't know.
ما هذه الأسافين، لا أعرف.
The length of the color sections don't make sense either.
طول المقاطع اللونية غير منطقي.
Somehow 156 is the same as 292, and almost as large as 957,
بطريقة ما 156 هو نفس 292، وتماثل تقريبًا حجم 957،
then to read this text you have to turn your head over weird.
ولقراءة هذا النص، أدر رأسك.
Here Fox News is indicating that the tax rate would increase by 5 times,
تشير هنا Fox News إلى أن معدل الضريبة سيرتفع 5 مرات،
except that the change is only from 35 to 39%.
باستثناء أن التغيير لا يتعدى 35 إلى 39?.
You assume the bottom of the graph of is 0, but here it's actually 34%.
كما أنك تفترض أن الجزء السفلي من الرسم البياني هو 0، بينما هو في الواقع 34?.
Thus leading us into believing this is huge change,
وهذا يقودنا إلى الاعتقاد بأن هذا تغيير كبير،
when it's actually quite small.
بينما الحقيقة هو أنه صغير.
These are examples of poor design.
هذه أمثلة على التصميم السيء.
In this lesson, I'll show you how to avoid making these mistakes and
وفي هذا الدرس، سأوضح لك كيفية تجنب ارتكاب هذه الأخطاء
instead, design your visualizations to be informative, accurate and
وبدلًا من ذلك، تصميم المرئيات الخاصة بك لتكون معلوماتية ودقيقة
visually appealing.
وجذابة بصريًا.